planetnatural.com 2006-03-15

# Planet Natural -- Privacy Policy

**Organic Lawn Care**  
  Lawn Fertilizers  
  Weed Control  
**Soil Care& Fertilizers**  
  Advanced Nutrients  
  Dry Fertilizers  
  Foliar Fertilizers  
  Houseplant Fertilizer  
  Hydroponic Nutrients  
  Liquid Fertilizers  
  Nutrient Supplements  
  Organic Fertilizers  
  Soil pH & Soil Test Kits  
  Soil & Soil Amendments  
**Composting**  
  Compost Bins  
  Compost Equipment  
  Worm Composting  
**Greenhouse Supply**  
  Cold Frames & Accessories  
  Greenhouses  
**Heirloom Seeds**  
  Heirloom Flower Seeds  
  Heirloom Herb Seeds  
  Heirloom Vegetable Seeds  
  Organic Seeds  
**Natural Pest Control**  
  Barriers & Repellents  
  Beneficial Insects  
  Biological Pest Control  
  Fungicides & Plant Disease  
  Home Pest Control  
  Insect Traps & Lures  
  Natural Pesticides  
  Soaps, Oils & More!  
**Garden Supplies**  
  Gardening Equipment  
  Plant Protection  
  Seed Starting  
  Sprayers & Applicators  
**Indoor Garden Supply**  
  Air & Water Pumps  
  Climate Controllers  
  CO2 Systems  
  EC, TDS & pH Meters  
  Growing Media  
  Hydroponic Supplies  
  Hydroponic Systems  
  Plant Propagation & Cloning  
**Grow Lights**  
  Accessories & Parts  
  Fluorescent & Spot Lighting  
  Grow Light Reflectors  
  Grow Light Remote Ballasts  
  Grow Light Systems  
  HPS Lamps & MH Bulbs  
**Healthy Homes**  
  Earth-Friendly Products  
  Natural Cleaning Products  
**Natural Pet Care**  
  Natural Flea Control  
  Pet Shampoo & Pet Supplies  
**OMRI Listed**  
**Bookstore**  
**Planet Natural Gear**  
**Gift Certificate**  
|  | |    
|   
  
---  
Planet Natural respects your privacy and recognizes your need for appropriate protection and management of your personal information such as your name, address, credit card, and e-mail. We recognize that when you choose to provide us with information about yourself, you trust us to act in a responsible manner. Planet Natural has created this policy to inform you how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our web site.  
  
**Information We Collect**  
  
We intend to give you as much control as possible over your personal information. In general, you can visit Planet Natural on the web without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. Consistent with most sites, we do log your internet address to give us an idea of which parts of our web site you visit and how long you spend there, but we do not link your internet address of your computer to anything personally identifiable.

There are times when we request that you voluntarily provide information such as your name, address, credit card, and e-mail. Generally this information is requested when you register for an on-line service or when you provide information in connection with an on-line transaction. Planet Natural may occasionally use this information for internal marketing purposes, including our e-mail newsletter and catalog mailing. Planet Natural will never sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others.  
  
**Security of Data**  
  
This site has reasonable security measures in place to protect the unauthorized access loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.

On-line transactions are safe with our secure shopping cart. This cart eliminates the possibility, however small, that someone might capture and view your personal information (such as a credit card number) while it is en route over the internet.  
  
**Links**  
  
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Planet Natural is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site.  
  
**Policy Subject to Change**  
  
If we decide to change our privacy practices, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always kept informed of what data we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Please check this page for changes from time to time to make sure you are aware of our latest privacy practices.

We are committed to continuing to protect the privacy of our customers. If you have any additional questions, please contact us at e-mail: [info@planetnatural.com](mailto:info@planetnatural.com)  

Copyright © 2004-2006 Sparky Boy Enterprises. All rights reserved.
